(Howard:)It's my mom's furniture.
(Howard:)It belongs in the house
I grew up in--
next to that pile of TV Guides
(Howard:)and in plain view of what,
for a ten-year-old, was
(Howard:)a quality piece
of string art!
(Bernadette:)Howie, if the store succeeds,
Stuart has a source of income,
(Bernadette:)and he can move out
of your mother's house.
(Bernadette:)Seems like some old furniture
is a reasonable price
(Bernadette:)to pay for that.
(Howard:)That is a good point.
(Howard:)But I didn't marry you
for good points.
(Howard:)I married you
to blindly support me
(Howard:)no matter how ridiculous
I'm being!
(Bernadette:)This is why I had
to rewrite our wedding vows.
(Leonard:)Hi, we're here to pick up
an order for Comic Center.
(Waitress:)Sure, let me go check on that.
Dude, I-I think
that's Nathan Fillion.
(Leonard:)Oh yeah,
look at that.
(gasps) And he's picking
the tomatoes out of his salad
(Raj:)just like I do.
(Raj:)I always did feel
a connection with him.
(Raj:)Oh, I have got
an idea.